<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="traffic_rules_final">
        Traffic signs tell you about traffic rules, hazards, where
you are, how to get where you are going, and where services
are located. The shape and color of these signs give clues
to the type of information they provide.\n\n

        There are traffic rules that say where, when and how fast
you can drive. These rules help to keep traffic moving safely.
Rules of the road include traffic controls, lane controls, rightof-way laws, and parking rules.\n\n

        Traffic controls include traffic signals, traffic signs and
pavement markings. Traffic control also can be provided
by law enforcement, highway personnel or school crossing
guards. You must obey directions from these persons.\n\n

        Red\n
Stop, yield or do what is shown on the sign.\n\n

Green\n
Direction. These signs indicate where a place is,
or how far a place is from where you are.\n\n

Blue\n
Services for travelers. These signs direct you to
places such as rest areas, tourist sites, hospitals,
hotels, gas stations, eating places, campgrounds
or picnic areas.\n\n

Yellow\n
General warning.\n\n

Fluorescent Yellow-Green\n
Pedestrian, bicycle and school warning signs.
The new color for these signs is much easier to
see in low light and foggy/rainy weather.\n\n

White\n
These signs include information regarding
enforceable laws and ordinances.\n\n

Orange\n
Road work, temporary traffic control, and
maintenance warnings. Be sure to watch for
workers on the road.\n\n

Brown\n
Recreation and cultural points of interest. These
signs point out historical sites, parks or recreational areas.\n\n

        Standard Shapes\n\n
Octagon - Stop\n
Come to a full stop at an intersection
controlled by this sign. Stop at the
marked stop line or before entering
the crosswalk or before your vehicle
enters the intersection. Let other
vehicles or pedestrians pass if they
are in your path.\n\n

Equilateral triangle\n
Yield the right of way. Slow down
and let vehicles crossing your path
go by. If necessary, stop before
going ahead. If pedestrians are in
or about to enter the crosswalk,
stop until they have crossed the
roadway, then proceed.\n\n

Pennant\n
This sign will be on the left-hand
side of the road or highway. It warns
you of a no passing zone.\n\n

Diamond\n
Warning. These signs alert you to
special road hazards. Words or
pictures on the sign will show you
why you need to slow down or use
extra caution.\n\n

Rectangle\n
Regulatory or guide. Vertical
signs indicate what you should or
should not do. Horizontal signs
give directions or information
about services drivers may want.\n\n

Pentagon\n
School crossing. Signs mark school
areas and school crossings. The
color of this sign may also be yellow.\n\n

Crossbuck\n
Railroad crossing signs are placed
at each crossing. A number sign
under the crossbucks shows how
many sets of train tracks you must
cross.\n\n

Circle\n
Railroad crossing ahead. These
signs give you early warning of
railroad crossings.\n\n

    </string>
</resources>